---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
|                            New BEAUVOIR Theme V2                              |
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
| Skinned by Arnaud BEAUVOIR - http://forum.beauvoir.net - contact@beauvoir.net |
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-- English --

Thank you to let the copyright in place on the login page and in all sources of
pages. This skin is the work of an author, thank you to respect it and not to
remove the copyright, or worse, to put your name at the place.

-- Deutsche --

Danke lassen Sie das copyright im Platz auf dem LOGON paginieren und in allen
Quellen der Seiten. Diese Haut ist die Arbeit eines Autors, danke, sie zu
respektieren und das copyright nicht zu entfernen, oder schlechter, um Ihren
Namen am Platz zu setzen.

-- Français --

Merci de laisser le copyright en place sur la page de connexion et dans toutes
les sources des pages. Ce skin est le travail d'un auteur, merci le respecter et
de ne pas enlever le copyright, ou pire, mettre votre nom à la place.

-- Español --

Gracias deje el copyright en lugar en la conexión paginar y en todas las fuentes
de páginas. Esta piel es el trabajo de un autor, gracias respetarlo y no quitar
el copyright, o peor, para poner su nombre en el lugar.

-- Português --

Obrigado deixe o copyright no lugar no início de uma sessão paginar e em todas as
fontes das páginas. Esta pele é o trabalho de um autor, obrigado respeitá-lo e
não remover o copyright, ou mais mau, para pôr seu nome no lugar.

-- Italian --

Grazie lasci il copyright sul posto alla pagina di inizio attività ed in tutte le
fonti delle pagine. Questa pelle è il lavoro di un autore, grazie rispettarlo e
non rimuovere il copyright, o più difettoso, per mettere il vostro nome al posto.

-- Russe --

Вы препятствуйте авторскому праву in place на странице login и в всех источниках
страниц. Эта кожа будет работой автора, вы уважать ее и не извлекать авторское
право, или плох, для того чтобы положить ваше имя на место.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
